<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Assignments on EPSY 630 - Statistics II</title>
    <link>/assignments/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Assignments on EPSY 630 - Statistics II</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/assignments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework</title>
      <link>/assignments/homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assignments/homework/</guid>
      <description>Homework 1 - DAACS Due January 27th
Go to demo.daacs.net, create an account, and complete the self-regulated learning and mathematics assessments. When done, enter your name and email address used to create an account on the DAACS website below. This is an ungraded assignment (i.e. you get credit for completing the assessments, not for the results). Click here to submit
Homework 2 - Inference for Numerical Data Due February 17th</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labs</title>
      <link>/assignments/labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assignments/labs/</guid>
      <description>Lab 1 - Intro to R and RStudio Due February 3rd
Click here to download the lab files. Once downloaded, open the intro_to_r.Rmd file, read, and complete the questions throughout the document. Click here to submit lab 1.
Lab 8 - Linear Regression Due February 24th
You can start the lab by running the following command in RStudio:
DATA606::startLab(&#39;Lab8&#39;)  Click here to submit lab 8.
Lab 9 - Multiple Regression Due March 30th</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation</title>
      <link>/assignments/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assignments/presentation/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of the data project is for you to conduct a reproducible analysis with a data set of your choosing. There are two components to the project, the proposal, which will be graded on a pass/fail basis, and the final report. The outline for each of these are provided in the templates. When submitting the assignments, include the R Markdown file (change the name to include your last name, for example Bryer-Proposal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>