<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EPSY 630 - Statistics II</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on EPSY 630 - Statistics II</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework</title>
      <link>/assignments/homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assignments/homework/</guid>
      <description>Homework 1 - DAACS Due January 27th
Go to demo.daacs.net, create an account, and complete the self-regulated learning and mathematics assessments. When done, enter your name and email address used to create an account on the DAACS website below. This is an ungraded assignment (i.e. you get credit for completing the assessments, not for the results). Click here to submit
Homework 2 - Inference for Numerical Data Due February 17th</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linear Regression</title>
      <link>/topics/linear_regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/topics/linear_regression/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labs</title>
      <link>/assignments/labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assignments/labs/</guid>
      <description> Lab 1 - Intro to R and RStudio Due February 3rd
Click here to download the lab files. Once downloaded, open the intro_to_r.Rmd file, read, and complete the questions throughout the document. Click here to submit lab 1.
Lab 8 - Linear Regression Due February 24th
You can start the lab by running the following command in RStudio:
DATA606::startLab(&#39;Lab8&#39;)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation</title>
      <link>/assignments/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assignments/presentation/</guid>
      <description>TBD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>/getting_started/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting_started/software/</guid>
      <description>R and RStudio  R - Windows or Mac RStudio - Download Windows or Mac version from here  If using Windows, you also need to download and install these:
 RTools ActivePerl  R Packages Once R is installed, install the following R packages.
install.packages(c(&#39;devtools&#39;, &#39;tidyverse&#39;, &#39;psych&#39;, &#39;reshape2&#39;, &#39;blogdown&#39;, &#39;bookdown&#39;, &#39;shiny&#39;, &#39;markdown&#39;, &#39;knitr&#39;, &#39;foreign&#39;, &#39;openintro&#39;, &#39;OIdata&#39;, &#39;fivethirdyeight&#39;)) devtools::install_github(&#39;jbryer/likert&#39;) devtools::install_github(&amp;quot;jbryer/DATA606&amp;quot;)  LaTeX LaTeX is a typesetting language for preparing documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data</title>
      <link>/getting_started/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting_started/data/</guid>
      <description>Programme of International Student Assessment Click here to go to the download page for the 2015 PISA results. Results from 2012, 2009, 2006, 2003, and 2000 are also available. Download the SPSS version of the files. You will also want to download the codebook files.
FiveThirtyEight FiveThirtyEight makes a lot of their datasets freely available. There is also an R package that has some of those datasets preformatted for R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/getting_started/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting_started/resources/</guid>
      <description>Books Wickham, H., &amp;amp; Grolemund, G. (2016) R for Data Science. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly.
 Most of this books is available freely online at r4ds.had.co.nz/ but can be purchased from Amazon.
 Wickham, H. (2014) Advanced R. Baca Raton, FL: Taylor &amp;amp; Francis Group.
 Most of this book is available freely online at adv-r.had.co.nz but can be purchased from Amazon.
 James, G., Witten, D., Hastie, T., &amp;amp; Tibshirani, R. (2013).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Equations</title>
      <link>/getting_started/mathjax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting_started/mathjax/</guid>
      <description>Occasionally you will need to type equations in homework and labs. R Markdown supports LaTeX style equations using the MathJax javascript library. I do not expect you to learn LaTeX for this course. Instead, I recommend using the free application Daum Equation Editor. It availabe online, as a Google Chrome Extension, or as a standalone Mac Application.
Creating Equations with Daum Equation Editor Occasionally you will need to type equations in homework and labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>This schedule is tentative and is subject to change. Last updated February 17, 2020 08:13AM
  Date Topic Resources    Mon, Jan 27 Intro to the Course / Intro to R and Rstudio Intro Course Slides, Intro R Slides  Mon, Feb 03 Central Limit Theorem Diez, et al Chapter 5Survey Results, Slides  Mon, Feb 10 Null hypothesis testing  Confidence Intervals Diez, et al Chapter 7  Mon, Feb 17 Linear Regression Diez, et al Chapter 8  Mon, Feb 24 Multiple Regression Diez, et al Chapter 9  Mon, Mar 02 TBD   Mon, Mar 09 Maximum Likelihood estimationLogistic Regression Diez, et al Chapter 9  Mon, Mar 16 NO CLASS - Spring Break   Mon, Mar 23 ANOVA Navarro Chapter 14Diez, et al Chapter 7.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>